tixr.com 2019-10-31

# Tixr | Privacy Policy

### Owner and Data Processor

Tixr Inc, 225 Santa Monica Blvd Suite 200, Santa Monica, CA 90401  
Owner contact email: [dpo@tixr.com](mailto:dpo@tixr.com)

### Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies and Usage Data.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.

Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Website.

Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Website is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services. In cases where this Website specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.

Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.

Read More

Read Less

### Mode and place of processing the Data

Any use of Cookies — or of other tracking tools — by this Website or by the owners of third-party services used by this Website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Website and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

Read More

Read Less

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.

The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

Read More

Read Less

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (âopt-outâ), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;

provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;

processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;

processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;

processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

Read More

Read Less

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

Read More

Read Less

### Retention time

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

  * **Therefore:**
  * Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
  * Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner's legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.
  * The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

Read More

Read Less

### The purposes of processing

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services (which includes providing End User Data collected to the event promoter/producer) as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Displaying content from external platforms, Handling payments, and Access to third-party accounts.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

Read More

Read Less

### Facebook permissions asked by this Website

This Website may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User's Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it. This service allows this Website to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

For more information about the following permissions, refer to the Facebook permissions documentation and to the Facebook privacy policy.

The permissions asked are the following:

  * **Basic information**
  * By default, this includes certain User's Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the User has made more of their Data public, more information will be available.
  * **About Me**
  * Provides access to the 'About Me' section of the profile.

Read More

Read Less

### Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

**Access to third-party accounts**

  * This type of service allows this Website to access Data from your account on a third-party service and perform actions with it.
  * These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.
  * **Facebook account access (this Website)**
  * This service allows this Website to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.
  * Permissions asked: About Me.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php). Privacy Shield participant.

**Displaying content from external platforms**

  * This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.
  * This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
  * **Google Maps widget (Google Inc.)**
  * Google Maps is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

**Infrastructure monitoring**

  * This type of service allows this Website to monitor the use and behavior of its components so its performance, operation, maintenance and troubleshooting can be improved.
  * Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and mode of implementation of these services, whose function is to filter the activities of this Website.
  * **New Relic (New Relic)**
  * New Relic is a monitoring service provided by New Relic Inc.
  * The way New Relic is integrated means that it filters all traffic of this Website, i.e., communication between the Application and the User's browser or device, while also allowing analytical data on this Website to be collected.
  * Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

**Analytics**

  * The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
  * **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**
  * Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (âGoogleâ). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
  * Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) — [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Privacy Shield participant.
  * **Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook, Inc.)**
  * Facebook Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on this Website.
  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.
  * **Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google Inc.)**
  * Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Website.
  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
  * Place of processing: United States — [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

**Handling payments**

  * Payment processing services enable this Website to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, this Website shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.
  * Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment.
  * **Braintree (PayPal Inc.)**
  * Braintree is a payment service provided by Braintree, a division of PayPal, Inc.
  * Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
  * Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy — [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/privacy).

Read More

Read Less

### In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.

Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.

Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.

Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.

Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.

Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.

Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User's consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.

Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

Read More

Read Less

### Details about the right to object to processing

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

Read More

Read Less

### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

Read More

Read Less

### Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services.

The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### How âDo Not Trackâ requests are handled

This Website does not support âDo Not Trackâ requests.

To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the âDo Not Trackâ requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User's consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

Read More

Read Less

### Definitions and legal references

**Personal Data (or Data)** : Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number â allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

**Usage Data** : Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

**User** : The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

**Data Subject** : The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

**Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)** : The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body transition-content which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

**Data Controller (or Owner)** : The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body transition-content which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website.

**This Website (or this Application)** : The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

**Service** : The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

**European Union (or EU)** : Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

**Cookies** : Small sets of data stored in the User's device.

**Legal information** : This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

Read More

Read Less

This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document. Generated with [iubenda](https://www.iubenda.com/) May 24, 2018.
